Viewers all over the world, open your lips.
Your human eyes can be blind to His acts of mercy,
to His acts of blessing, to His acts of salvation.
Lift up your voice and ask the Lord to restore your sight so that you can feel His touch,
so that you will hear Him say, "You are healed; you are blessed!"
Open your lips!
Restore my sight, Lord!
Restore my sight, Lord, to feel Your touch and hear You say we are delivered!
Open your lips!
Restore my sight, Lord!
Viewers, every spirit that stands against you, every spirit that challenges you,
every spirit that challenges your career,
every spirit that stands against you, that stands against your business -
loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Leave my people!
You demon, leave my people!
Leave their career!
I say, Leave my people!
Begin to break any contact, whatever contact!
You are a child of God - take your dominion!
Say, "No!"
Break whatever contact!
Be it in your business - break it!
Be it in your family - break it!
Be it in your career - break it!
Be it in your health - break it!
Prayer - begin to break it!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever that disease is located, wherever that infirmity,
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Hear the voice of God, you disease!
You infirmity, hear the voice of God!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In your blood, in your kidneys, in your liver, in your bones - out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
I cover myself with the blood of Jesus.
Feel His touch, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.